# HASHEM AL-SAQQA

#### ANDROID DEVELOPER



+972592989725 hashem.b.saqqa@gmail.com Gaza, Palestine

## **OBJECTIVE**

Android development expert with technical skills in gathering system requirements and logical data. I have a very strong knowledge of API. I have built multiple Applications using java and UI/UX designs. With such a strong knowledge in my career, I am dedicated, People-focused, and detail-oriented, a hard worker, a responsible person and have a stable, personal life, and learn incredibly quickly.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

Android Developer Freelancer 2020-01 - now

Teacher Assistance in computer engineering University College of Applied Sciences / Gaza, Palestine 2022-02 - now

Technical Trainer - Mobile development UNRWA - KYTC / Gaza, Palestine 2022-3

#### **SKILLS**

- •Android java
- •Restful API
- Firebase
- SQLite
- •postman
- •Material Design
- •GitHub

- Google Maps
- Notifications
- •Responsive layout for different screens
- •Extracting design from XD or PSD file
- Room database
- project analysis



# **EDUCATION**

2017 - 2021 Bachelor /computer science Islamic university

2021 - now Master / Data science Islamic university

## **LANGUAGE**

- Arabic, native
- English, fluent

#### **PROJECTS**

- Event sheet
- Weather app
- Chat app
- Meals recipes
- Ajeer
- Pearling